I have a bit of a dirty little secret.
There is someone on the internet
that I've been copying for over two years,
and I
made millions from it. So in this video,
I'm going to credit exactly everything
I've stolen and why,
and I'm going to come clean about it to
help me sleep better
at night. So this is Ed.
You would've heard me reference him in
some videos before,
but I've never truly given him the amount
of credit really required for the amount
of thefts that have occurred.
And just one of the most recent thefts
allowed me to make $7,500 in 12 hours from
a
video here that you can see
is a 10 out of 10.
For any of you that don't use YouTube,
that means that's the worst performing
video
out of the last 10,
yet it's netted some of the most income in
the smallest amount
of hours. And even any of you
that have noticed,
I now have two YouTube channels.
Again, I stole that from Ed.
So let's rewind to 2023.
Just before I killed my podcast,
I decided to ask Ed
if he wanted to come on and
have a chat. The reason being is,
I'm not going to say I was driving,
could be
illegal. I was in my car.
I can even tell you the exact video
that I saw first.
It was from his previous channel called
Film Booth, and it was either the silent
hack YouTubers use to hook you, or it
was editing mistakes 71% of
YouTubers make.
You can see both those videos did over a
million views.
So I watched that video. First, abrupt
and say,
"Watch this video next because it's
going to tell you how-
Then at the end of that video,
he told me to watch another
one, so I watched another one.
It then got to the end of that video,
end up
watching another, and
that happened maybe 10 times.
So then when I invited Ed to come on a
podcast, I think he said his ex-girlfriend
followed me. I said, "Mate,
I watched 12 of your videos today.
Isn't that amazing?" And he says to me,
"Yeah, that's intentional.
I call it the binge effect." We did the
podcast and regrettably, barely anyone
listened to it,
as I later found out why through working
with Ed.
And after the call, I said,
"How can I work with you?" He goes, "Oh,
well this is
how much it is, and then I have a really,
really expensive package that's 10,000 US
dollars." Now,
here's the thing I need to admit.
Up until this point,
I never believed in courses.
I never believed in paying some person on
the internet for some videos.
But I was so taken aback to how much those
10 binge-worthy videos had captured
me that I was like, "Do you know what?
You son of a bitch.
I'm in." I joined Ed's course,
and I'll be honest, I never even joined
the Discord. I just learnt from him.
And in silent, without being big-headed,
I was probably one of his most successful
students. You can see
that I created YouTube.
I don't know what the hell I
was doing for years. For years.
I actually also got locked out of it.
That's another story altogether.
This is a bit of a better visual
representation.
I had a couple videos that booted off,
and then just towards 2023, what was the
date that I did the podcast with Ed?
Just around here,
I started working with Ed.
As you can see, channel boomed for a year,
and then it died, and I'll explain why
in a second.
It says this channel's made £96,000.
Who's got that? I haven't.
Be having a word with my manager after
this.
Now if we break it down into revenue,
started his course in June,
that August, had a 10, give or take,
a £10,000
YouTube month. Well, considering it
was only 10,000 US dollars,
I made my entire
investment from Ed's course back in just
one month of AdSense.
Not to mention the benefits
that could've had to my business around
the board.
So regrettably, at 32,
maybe even 33 years old, for the first
time, I came to believe
that paying a stranger on the internet a
vast amount of
money can mean that you can make a vast
amount of money.
So you're probably thinking why am I
making this video?
Technically,
I hired Ed to help me with my YouTube,
but he didn't help me with my
YouTube. Well, he did.
He helps me with everything by helping me
with
my YouTube. First of all,
he gave me the belief
and the tools in an area that was
my weakness for a very long time,
and by developing that weak part of my
brand and business,
it definitely gave me some more
confidence.
But whilst doing one-to-one calls with Ed,
he said two things.
One, what does this channel sell? And two,
where is your course?
Now, annoyingly, I was like, "Ah,
you're right.
I've kind of grown a channel just trying
to be famous." Actually, what I've tried
to do is grow a channel so I can get a
gold play button.
Quite literally, that
was the purpose of the channel.
And what happens there is,
when you make videos in a bid to go viral,
you just get
people that want to watch viral videos.
So here's some of the crazy side tangents.
I still talk to Ed.
Was chatting to him last night.
This is an AI image of me,
and I messaged Ed.
I saw an AI image of him.
I was like, "Mate, how
are you doing this?" And he goes, "Mate,
log into the
course." And he goes,
"It's in the module." I was like,
"What?" He's like, "Yeah,
I've updated the course."
And I'm not going to lie to you,
I've probably done this
course three times now in two years.
So the fact that Ed said to me,
"Although you paid back in 2023,
you can now
log in and get a brand new course,"
that then made me realize I need to raise
the
standard of my own course.
If Ed's doing it, I should be doing it.
It's not so much
that I copied his information, it's
that I copied his work ethos.
It definitely rubbed off on me.
I would say in the world of social media
creation
and running a business,
I may be like a purple or brown belt,
and Ed's the black
belt. He's the person I go to.
Don't get me wrong,
the majority of people on the
internet I could give sound advice to,
but when things get really technical, I
stand in a position where I go, "Oh,
do you know what?
You probably need Ed."
And that's kind of what this video is.
So whilst I was having my existential
crisis, Ed,
who has his massive channel with
376,000 subscribers goes,
"Do you know what?
I'm going to splinter off
and start a brand new channel because it's
not about
getting a gold play button,
it's about getting clients."
And he kind of drilled
into me that it's not about getting
massive amounts of views, it's about just
having an impact on someone
that can help their life.
And to do so,
you need to have quite targeted content
that is not optimized for
views,
but optimized to help your demographic.
So my small channel was born,
which I haven't even monetized.
And the interesting thing is, Ed,
in his own content, explains the fact
that sometimes his videos with less views
make him more money because they're more
geared towards making sales than they
are geared towards being famous.
So 12 hours ago,
I decided to make a video which,
as far as YouTube
standards, has bombed,
but as far as financial standards,
has made me nearly
$10,000 in 12 hours.
It's only got me two subscribers, and I
suppose the reason for me talking about
this is I'm so eternally grateful that Ed
broke apart my detachment from success
being connected to views,
virality, or followers,
and connected me with the idea of getting
clients that you
can help.
It was a year since starting Ed's course
that I even launched
my own mentorship. It was the belief,
the lessons, the tools, and
probably a good year of posting videos.
I'll show you something I haven't really
showed anyone before.
If you look here at the status of these
videos, almost all of them are
private,
and they're private because I hate them
And I hate them because I'm
embarrassed by them,
and I'm embarrassed by them because
they're terrible.
And they're terrible because I
was just flinging shit at a wall,
hoping things
would stick.
And you could look at these as massive
wastes of time.
But I'm eternally grateful to this
because, again, Ed
was one of the first people
that ever drilled into me,
it's better to put out content,
make mistakes, and fall
forward. It's better to welcome mistakes.
It's better to embrace mistakes.
It's better to just get active.
I've been in business 10 years online,
digitally.
I'm still very much a student.
I'm still learning things as time goes on.
And if it wasn't for me having my beliefs
broken down into the online
course bro world,
I don't know where I'd be.
Obviously,
I'd still be living in Australia,
et cetera.
But I feel like the training wheels have
been taken off my mind to the online space
of YouTube and wider and business.
The return that I've made since doing Ed's
course isn't just the high
AdSense month that I had a couple months
later.
In the past two years,
I am millions of dollars better off
from a 10 grand investment.
That's my point. I'm not saying
that all courses.
I would know. I've done all courses.
It's not just a course you're buying,
it's belief that you're buying.
It's lessons that you're buying.
I even remember doing a one-to-one with Ed
where I
said to him, "Mate,
I'm not going to lie to you,
my comments have gone to shit." He
goes, "Good. Means
that you've reached a cold audience.
Means that the algorithm's pushing your
content." I was like, you know what?
Just that alone was probably worth the
$1,000 US dollars I paid him for the phone
call. Now, of course,
the backbone of this video
is promoting me and my services
and my course. But actually,
the thing was,
so much of what I've accomplished over
the last few years,
I kind of want to attribute to Ed.
But he didn't make the videos for me.
He didn't do my editing for me.
He didn't come up with the ideas in the
shower.
He just gave me the tools for me to make
that happen myself.
For so many of you watching this,
you probably have everything you need for
success,
just not the tools to make it happen over
the next two years.
If you are specifically looking to grow on
YouTube, I might even say
you're better off with Ed.
But then I'd say if you have the nuances
closer to some
of the businesses that I've operated,
whether that's a drinks brand, fitness
business, online course, physio, golf,
sport,
jujitsu,
you're probably better off with mine.
But the sole purpose of this video
is I'm not just selling a course and a
mentorship because it makes me money.
I'm selling this because quite literally,
one of these didn't just change my
life, changed my revenue,
changed what car I drive,
changed the status of my
mortgage,
changed where I sat on the plane,
even changes the level of respect which
other business owners give me now.
And I can't promise
that you're one digital course away from
making millions, but
could be a few hours studying
and a few months trial
and erroring away from a
completely different life.
And that's something
that you shouldn't take lightly.
Going to put a link to Ed's channels in
the description.
Going to put a link to his course.
I might even put a link to his email list,
which
I'm not on because I just can't take any
more inspiration from it at this point.
Otherwise, I'm going to end up like
that dude that stole my transcript.
And again,
this video isn't optimized for views.
It's just optimized for the truth.
If you like this,
you might love my other videos,
and YouTube recommends that
you'll enjoy this one here.
And even pointing at this video here.
Yep, I learned that from Ed.